socialseo.com 2018-08-15

# Privacy Policy

## SocialSEO Privacy Policy

Last updated 3.22.17

SocialSEO operates https://www.socialseo.com (the “Site”)

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. We use your collected information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you  
agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy.

### Log Data

Like many site operators, we collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site (“Log Data”).  This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.  In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this.

### Cookies

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier.  Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.  Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

### Communications

If you provide us with your Personal Information or contact information, we may contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that is of a commercial nature.  You can choose to no longer receive this material at any time by contacting us at inquiries@socialseo.com, clicking “unsubscribe” in the email or calling us as 719-725-6400 or by mail sent to

SocialSEO, 5475 Mark Dabling Blvd #210, Colorado Springs, CO, 80918

### Scholarship Applicants

All SocialSEO scholarship applicants (SocialSEO Digital Marketing and SEO Scholarship) who provide personal information to SocialSEO will not be contacted for any reason other than as it directly relates to the scholarship process. Personal information of scholarship applicants will not be distributed, sold or given to any 3rd parties.  All Personal Information collected from scholarship applicants will not be used for any purpose other than awarding the annual scholarship.

### Security

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but  no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect all information collected, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of March 22, 2017 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page.  We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy.
